Guide to the South Asian Pamphlets Collection, 1920-2005 (bulk 1950-2000) RL.01235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Pakistan Pamphlets, 1948-2005, bulk 1960s-1990s, 58 boxes
  - Education, 1952-1994, 5 boxes
    - Towards ISLESCO for the Revival of Islamic Values in Education, Science, and Culture. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Karachi, Hamdard Foundation Press, Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-17)
    - University Grants Commission and National Academy of Higher Education Publications. Ahmad, Ishtiaq. Islamabad, University Grants Commission, Pakistan: 1991. (Box PA-18)
      5th edition.
    - University of Islamabad, The: Calendar 1970-71. Islamabad. University of Islamabad. Islamabad, Registrar of University of Islamabad, Pakistan: 1970? (Box PA-18)
    - University of Islamabad. Islamabad, University of Islamabad, Pakistan: 1975. (Box PA-18)
    - University of Peshawar Ordinance, 1973, The: N.W.P.F. Ordinance No. II of 1974: An Ordinance to Reconstitute and Reorganize the University of Peshawar. North-west Frontier Province. Peshawar, Government Stationary and Print Department.Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-18)
    - Vocational Subjects (Industrial Group) Drafting Trades Group Curricula for Classes IX-X. Islamabad. National Bureau of Curriculum and Textbooks. Islamabad, Ministry of Education & Provincial Coordination, Pakistan: 1977. (Box PA-18)
    - Vocational Subjects (Industrial Group) Electrical Trades Group Curricula for Classes IX-X. Islamabad. National Bureau of Curriculum and Textbooks. Islamabad, Ministry of Education & Provincial Coordination, Pakistan: 1976. (Box PA-18)
    - Vocational Subjects (Industrial Group) Wood Trades Group Curricula for Classes IX-X. Islamabad. National Bureau of Curriculum and Textbooks. Islamabad, Ministry of Education & Provincial Coordination, Pakistan: 1976. (Box PA-18)
    - Welcome to Islamabad. Islamabad. Ministry of Education. Islamabad, Ministry of Education, Pakistan: 1989. (Box PA-18)
      National Education Conference.
  - Energy and Natural Resources, 1962-1990, 1 box
    These 26 pamphlets provide information on developing various sources of energy such as fossil, hydroelectric, nuclear and gobar gas, papers read at the National Seminar on Petrochemicals and national energy plans for self-sufficiency.
    - Arab Petrodollars: Dashed Hope for a New Economic Order. Lahore, Group 83. Lahore, Group 83, Pakistan: 1987. (Box PA-19)
      Group 83 Series.
    - Case Study of Petro-Chemical Project in Pakistan, A. Akhtar, Farruk S. M., andDin, Mohammad, and Chaudhry, Iqbal A. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
      National Seminar on Petrochemicals, April 12th and 13th 1981.
    - Concept of Planning and Implementation of Petro-Chemicals Manufactures in a Developing Country, A. Clough, H., and Hatton, S. A. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Economics and Interaction of Long Term Energy Supply and Petro-Chemical Production, The. Hak, Shahid K., and Yusufm, Akbar, and Haider, Waqar. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Facts about Pakistan. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1975? (Box PA-19)
      Atomic Energy.
    - 500 KV Faisalabad - Guddu Transmission Line. Pakistan. Water and Power Development Authority. Lahore, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-19)
    - Fuels and Minerals. Pakistan. Ministry Of Information And Broadcasting. Karachi, Pakistan: 1968. (Box PA-19)
    - Gobar Gas: An Alternate Way of Handling the Village Fuel Problem. Islamabad. Appropriate Technology Development Organization. Islamabad, Appropriate Technology Development Organization, Pakistan: 197-? (Box PA-19)
      Fertilizer and Fuel.
    - In the Service of Pakistan. Karachi. Public Relations Department. Karachi, Public Relations Department, Pakistan: 1969? (Box PA-19)
    - Introductory Speech. Mian, Maqsud A. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Nuclear Energy in Pakistan. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1979. (Box PA-19)
    - Oil Crisis, The. Husain, S. Irtiza. Islamabad, Institute of Strategic Studies, Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-19)
    - 100 Days in Power: Achievements of People's Government. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 199-? (Box PA-19)
      Energy: Ghazi-Barotha and Hub Hydropower Projects.
    - Pakistan: Energy Resources. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Pakistan: Water and Power. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1986. (Box PA-19)
    - Pakistani Coals for Petro-Chemicals and Energy. Mian, Maqsud A. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Pakistan's Nuclear Programme. Islamabad. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1987. (Box PA-19)
    - Petro-Chemicals Development in Pakistan. Haidari, Iqbal. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Petro-Chemicals Market in the 80's. Ahmad, Mahmood A., and Pervaiz, Sajid. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
    - Pinstech: 1965-85. Pakistan Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology. Pakistan Institute of Nuclear Science and Technology, Pakistan: 1986? (Box PA-19)
    - Presidential Address. Usmani, I. H. Lahore, Pakistan: 1962. (Box PA-19)
      Delivered at Cento Scientific Symposium.
    - Programme. Karachi. Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 19--? (Box PA-19)
    - Status and Prospects: Lakhra Coal Mine and Power Generation Project. Islamabad. United States Agency for International Development. Islamabad, United States Agency for International Development, Pakistan: 1985. (Box PA-19)
    - Summary of Feasibility Study for Setting Up of a Thermal Power Station in Makran Division. Pakistan Engineering Services Limited. Karachi, Pakistan Engineering Services Ltd., Pakistan: 1983. (Box PA-19)
    - Welcome Address. Chotani, A. H. Karachi, Pakistan Institute of Chemical Engineers, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-19)
  - Health, 1968-2005, 2 boxes
    The 48 pamphlets in this section provide information on hospitals, public and private health facilities, medical education, special needs of the disabled, conference papers, medical research, psychiatric treatment, drug addiction and rehabilitation, earthquake relief, Eastern medicine in a changing world, drug abuse prevention, diet, nutritional deficiencies and maternity care. Includes a Pakistan medical directory.
    - Aga Khan Hospital and Medical College, The. Karachi, The Aga Khan Hospital and Medical College, Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-20)
    - Aga Khan Maternity Home Karimabad Karachi, Pakistan, The. Karachi, The Aga Khan Maternity Home Karimabad, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-20)
    - Annual Convocation of College of Physicians and Surgeons, Pakistan, 1978, Held in Karachi on 4th January, 1979. [Karachi], College of Phsysicians and Surgeons, Pakistan: 1979? (Box PA-20)
      English or Urdu.
    - Blindness - Its Social Aspects. The Society for the Prevention & Cure of Blindness. Karachi, The Society for the Prevention & Cure of Blindness, Pakistan: 1971. (Box PA-20)
      Fourth Edition.
    - Brief History of the Activities and Annual Report of the West Pakistan Society for the Rehabilitation of the Disabled, A. Lahore, The West Pakistan Society for the Rehabilitation of the Disabled, Pakistan: 1972? (Box PA-20)
    - Cancer: The Last Two and a Half Millennia of Aetiology and Cure. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Karachi, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1979? (Box PA-20)
      Paper Presented at XII International Cancer Congress Buenos Aires - Argentina.
    - Centre for Speech and Hearing: Report for July 1984 to June 1985. Kulsoom, Margie. Pakistan, Centre for Speech and Hearing, Pakistan: 1986? (Box PA-20)
      Report for July 1984 to June 1985.
    - Community Rehabilitation of Psychiatric Patients- A Collaborative Study between Fountain House, New York and Fountain House, Lahore. Pakistan, Lahore Mental Health Association, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-20)
    - Concepts of Conservation in Children, A Cross-Cultural Perspective. Durani, Naeem. [n.p], Pakistan: 1983? (Box PA-20)
      Paper presented at the 5th Conference of Pakistan Psychological Association, May 4-6, 1983, Islamabad.
    - Drug Dependence in Pakistan. Khan, Zaheer. Islamabad, Pakistan Narcotics Control Board, Pakistan: 1984. (Box PA-20)
    - Earthquake Relief in Azad Kashmir and NWFP; Dialysis and Intensive Care at the Doorsteps of Disaster. Karachi, SIUT, Pakistan: 2005. (Box PA-20)
      Courtesy: Newsweek, October 24, 2005.
    - Eastern Medicine in a Changing World. Karachi, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1978? (Box PA-20)
      Paper presented by Hakim Mohammed Said at International Finnish Archipelago Conference, Turku-Finland, August 28-September 1, 1978.
    - Fawayid Al-Insan, The. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Karachi, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1979? (Box PA-20)
      Paper Presented at Second International Symposium for the History of Arabic Science Aleppo- Syria.
    - XVth Biennial Pakistan Medical Conference (P.M.A. Centre). Pakistan Medical Association. Lahore, Pakistan Medical Association, Pakistan: 1983? (Box PA-20)
      November 19-21, 1982.
    - First Anniversary and National Symposium, Green December Movement, December 1984, Peshawar; Annual Report 1984. [Peshawar], [Green December Movement], Pakistan: 1984? (Box PA-20)
    - First Health of the Nation Conference: First Annual Report 1971-72. Institute of Health and Tibbi (Medical) Research. Pakistan, Institute of Health and Tibbi (Medical) Research, Pakistan: 1972? (Box PA-20)
    - First National Convention of General Practiotioners/Family Physicians, 10th -12th January, 1975; Souvenir. Karachi, College of Family Medicine, Pakistan: 1975. (Box PA-20)
    - Five Years of Revolutionary Government: The Health Division, 1958-1963. [Islamabad], Department of Films and Publications, Pakistan: 1965. (Box PA-20)
    - Glimpses of Medicine through Archaeology. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Karachi, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1976? (Box PA-20)
      Paper presented by Hakim Mohammed Said at Fiftieth Anniversary of Archaeological Studies, University of Cairo, January 17-January 22, 1976.
    - Health. Pakistan. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Karachi, Pakistan: 1968. (Box PA-20)
    - Health and Medical Information Booklet. American Embassy, and American Consulate. Islamabad, American Embassy, Pakistan: 1992. (Box PA-20)
    - How the Society for Prevention and Cure of Blindness Was Established. [Karachi], Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-20)
    - Important Health Statistics of Pakistan. Chaudhary, Mushtaq Ahmad and Ahmad, Shamshad. Ministry of Labour, Manpower, Health and Population Planning, Pakistan: 1976. (Box PA-59 (oversize))
    - Joint Lahore-Peshawar P.M.A. Clinical Conference July 18-20, 1984, Lahore. Pakistan Medical Association. Lahore, Pakistan Medical Association, Pakistan: 1984. (Box PA-20)
    - Light, Knowledge, Truth. Zahibya, Risalaye. Karachi, Peermohammad Ebrahim Trust, Pakistan: 1968? (Box PA-20)
    - Medicinal Plant Resources of Pakistan. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Pakistan, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1979? (Box PA-20)
      Paper Presented at International Seminar on "Human and Natural Resources in the Muslim World" at Dacca, Bangladesh
    - Medicine at the Doorstep. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Pakistan, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1978? (Box PA-20)
      Paper Presented at VII International Congress of Rural Medicine at Salt Lake City, Utah, U.S.A.
    - NWFP Information Bulletin. N.W.F.P. Peshawar, Pakistan: 1984. (Box PA-20)
    - On Disaster Front: Report on Flood Relief Work. Pakistan Red Crescent Society. Lahore, Pakistan Red Cresesnt Society, Pakistan: 1977? (Box PA-20)
      On the organization and objectives of the PRCS; includes a report on its flood relief work in 1977.
    - PAEC Medical Centres in Pakistan; Planned; Under Construction. Islamabad, Pakistan: 1975. (Box PA-21)
    - Pakistan Fights Narcotics Menace. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 199-? (Box PA-21)
    - Pakistan Health Education Survey (PHES): Summary Report. Ministry of Health. Islamabad, Ministry of Health, Pakistan: 1992? (Box PA-21)
    - Pakistan Medical Directory, 1974. Pakistan, Pakistan Polyclinics Limited, Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-21)
    - Pakistan: Health and Social Welfare. Pakistan. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. Islamabad, Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-21)
    - Pakistan: Health. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Pakistan, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1984. (Box PA-21)
    - Press Kit. Drug Abuse Prevention Resource Centre. Islamabad, Drug Abuse Prevention Resource Centre, Pakistan: 1992. (Box PA-21)
    - Prevention and Cure of Blindness in Pakistan: Health Services Needed for Common Eye Diseases. The Society for the Prevention & Cure of Blindness. Karachi, The Society for the Prevention & Cure of Blindness, Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-21)
      This booklet is compiled from facts gathered from the Press and Literature issued by the Institutions in Pakistan and Foreign Countries concerned with Blindness.
    - Proceedings: Health of the Nation Conference. Health of the Nation Conference. Karachi, The Institute of Health and Tibbi Research, Pakistan: 1973. (Box PA-21)
      III, 21st March, 1973 thru 8th April, 1973.
    - Proceedings: Health of the Nation Conference. Health of the Nation Conference. Karachi, The Institute of Health and Tibbi Research, Pakistan: 1974. (Box PA-21)
      IV, 21st March, 1973 thru 8th April, 1973.
    - Programmes and Activities of National Institute of Psychology. Islamabad, Incharge Publications, Pakistan: 1988. (Box PA-21)
      Center of Excellence, Quaid-I-Azam University.
    - Protein Problem of Pakistan, Report of the Protein Committee Appointed by the National Science Council, Pakistan. National Science Council. Lyallpur, Pakistan: 1971. (Box PA-21)
    - Recommendations: First Health of the Nation Conference March 1971, Second Health of the Nation Conference March 1972. Institute of Health and Tibbi (Medical) Research. Karachi, Institute of Health and Tibbi (Medical) Research, Pakistan: 1973? (Box PA-21)
    - Role of Hospitals in Primary Health Care: International Conference Inaugural Address. Zia-Ul-Haq, General Mohammad. Islamabad, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-21)
    - Souvenir to Commemorate Sixth National Psychiatric Conference, 23-25 Oct, 1985, Quetta. Mujahid, A. S. Chishti, and Achakzi, A. Malik. Pakistan, Pakistan Psychiatric Society,Pakistan: 1985. (Box PA-21)
      Quetta - October 23-25, 1985.
    - Souvenir, The: 1980. The Hahnemannian Cancer Relief Society of Pakistan. Karachi, The Hahnemannian Cancer Relief, Pakistan: 1980? (Box PA-21)
    - Traditional Medicine in the Service of Health. Said, Hakim Mohammed. Pakistan, Hamdard National Foundation, Pakistan: 1978? (Box PA-21)
      Paper Presented at XXVIth International Congress of the History of Medicine at Plovdiv, Bulgaria.
    - Twelfth Annual Report of the Association for the Welfare of the Adult Deaf and Dumb, Karachi. Ali, Begum Raana Liaquat. Karachi, Association for the Welfare of the Adult Deaf and Dumb, Pakistan: 1974? (Box PA-21)
      For the year ended 30th June, 1973.
    - 25 Years of Leprosy Work in Pakistan: A Short History of the Marie Adelaide Leprosy Centre. Karachi, Marie Adelaide Leprosy Centre, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-21)
    - Unani, Ayurvedic and Homeopathic Systems of Medicine Rules, The. Ministry of Law and Parliamentary Affairs. Pakistan, Ministry of Law and Parliamentary Affairs, Pakistan: 1968. (Box PA-21)
      As modified up to the 29th May, 1968.
  - Industry, 1962-1983, 2 boxes
    The 37 pamphlets in this section discuss Pakistan's government policy on industry, research and development in industry and individual industries such as cement, mining, ceramics, cigarettes, wool, jute, minerals, bicycles and food products.
    - Atlas Group of Companies. Atlas Group. Karachi, Atlas Group, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-22)
    - Cement Industry in Pakistan. Ghani, M. A. Karachi, West Pakistan Industrial Development Corporation, Pakistan: 1968. (Box PA-22)
    - Census of Mining Industries, 1979-80. Pakistan. Federal Bureau of Statistics. Karachi, Pakistan: 1983. (Box PA-22)
    - Ceramics Industry in West Pakistan. Sheikh, Mohammad Ali. Lahore, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, Govt. of West Pakistan, Pakistan: 1969? (Box PA-22)
    - Cigarette Manufacturing Industry in West Pakistan. Hasan, Saeed Khawaja. West Pakistan, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, Pakistan: 197-? (Box PA-22)
    - Conditions of Contract Governing: Department of Investment Promotion and Supplies Contracts. Ministry of Industries. Department of Investment Promotion and Supplies. Karachi, Ministry of Industries, Department of Investment Promotion and Supplies, Pakistan: 1972. (Box PA-22)
    - Industrial Culture in Pakistan: Lessons for State Enterprise. Qureshi, Zafar Iqbal. Lahore, Punjab Adbi Markaz Book Shop, Pakistan: 1977. (Box PA-22)
    - Industrial Investment Opportunities in Pakistan: An Investment Guide. Bank of Credit and Commerce International Limited. Karachi, Bank of Credit and Commerce International Limited, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-22)
    - Industrial Production. Pakistan. Ministry Of Information And Broadcasting. Karachi, Pakistan: 1968. (Box PA-22)
    - International Seminar on Sheep & Wool, March 14-16, 1982, Souvenir. Pakistan Agricultural Research Council. Islamabad, Pakistan Agricultural Research Council, Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-22)
    - Jute Industry in Pakistan (1983). The Pakistan Jute Mills Association. Karachi, The Pakistan Jute Mills Association, Pakistan: 1983? (Box PA-22)
    - Marble Processing in Pakistan. Karachi, Investment Advisory Centre of Pakistan, Pakistan: 1967. (Box PA-22)
      Investment Portfolio Brief No. 5.
    - Mineral Wealth of The Province of Punjab. Shams, F. A. Lahore, Institute of Geology, University of Punjab, Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-22)
    - Minerals for Export. Karachi, Pakistan Mineral Development Corporation, Pakistan: 197-? (Box PA-22)
    - Optical Industry in West Pakistan. Aziz, Abdul. Lahore, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, Govt. of West Pakistan, Pakistan: 1970. (Box PA-22)
    - Pakchina Fertilizers Limited Haripur. National Fertilizer Corporation of Pakistan Limited. Pakistan, National Fertilizer Corporation of Pakistan Limited, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-22)
      A Project of National Fertilizer Corporation of Pakistan Limited.
    - Pakistan: Industry. Islamabad, Ministry of Information & Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1982? (Box PA-22)
    - Pakistan: Industry. Islamabad, Ministry of Information & Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1984. (Box PA-22)
    - Pakistan Standards Institution (Certification Marks): Rules and Regulations. Pakistan Standards Institution. Karachi, Pakistan: 1962. (Box PA-22)
      Published in the Official Gazette on July 6, 1962 and August 10, 1962 respectively.
    - Pakistan's Economy with Emphasis on Textile and Apparel Industry. Karachi, Pakistan Cotton Fashion Apparel Manufacturers & Exporters Association, Pakistan: 1988? (Box PA-23)
    - Paper and Board Industry In Pakistan. Haidari, Iqbal. Karachi, Economic and Industrial Publications, Pakistan: 1975. (Box PA-23)
    - PICIC at Work. Pakistan Industrial Credit & Investment Corporation Ltd. Pakistan, Pakistan Industrial Credit & Investment Corporation Ltd, Pakistan: 1965. (Box PA-23)
    - Project Profiles. Sind Small Industries Corporation. Karachi, Pakistan: 198-? (Box PA-23)
    - Prosperity through Industry. Imtiaz, Saadat Ali. Karachi, Public Relations Department, PIDC, Pakistan: 196-? (Box PA-23)
    - Quinquennial Digest (1978-83): Publications Technical Services & Promotional Activities. Pakistan Council of Scientific & Industrial Research. Karachi, PCSIR Directorate of Industrial Liaison, Pakistan: 1983? (Box PA-23)
    - Quinquennial Digest (1978-83): R & D Activities & Technical Services. Pakistan Council of Scientific & Industrial Research. Karachi, PCSIR Directorate of Industrial Liaison, Pakistan: 1983? (Box PA-23)
      Fruit Technology Division, Peshawar Laboratories.
    - Refractory Industry in West Pakistan. Sheikh, Mohammad Ali. Lahore, Govt. of West Pakistan, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, Pakistan: 1969. (Box PA-23)
    - Report of the Regional Workshop of Agricultural Machinery Manufacturers' Associations (First Session). Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific. Islamabad, Agricultural Machinery Division, Pakistan Agricultural Research Council and Regional Network for Agricultural Machinery (RNAM), Pakistan: 1982. (Box PA-23)
      7 September 1982.
    - Report on Bicycle Industry in Pakistan, A. Pakistan Industrial Credit And Investment Corporation Limited. Karachi, Economic and Research Department, Pakistan: 1978. (Box PA-23)
    - Research on Building Materials. Aslam, M. Karachi, Directorate of Industrial Liaison, Pakistan: 1981. (Box PA-23)
    - Small Scale Industry in Pakistan. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Islamabad, Pakistan: 1978. (Box PA-23)
    - Statement by the Chairman A. W. Adamjee on the Occasion of the Fifth Annual General Meeting Held on 27th April, 1963. Pakistan Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation Limited. Pakistan, Pakistan Industrial Credit and Investment Corporation Limited, Pakistan: 1963. (Box PA-23)
    - Sugar Industry In Pakistan. Haidari, Iqbal. Karachi, Pakistan: 1975. (Box PA-23)
      Incorporating Balance Sheet Analyses of 18 Sugra Mills Listed on Karachi Stock Exchange.
    - Vegetable Ghee Industry in West Pakistan. Ahmad, Mansur. Lahore, Govt. of West Pakistan, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, Pakistan: 1969. (Box PA-23)
    - West Pakistan Industrial Development Corporation: An Introduction. Karachi, Public Relations Department, WPIDC, Pakistan: 1971. (Box PA-23)
    - What Does It Mean. N.W.F.P. Small Scale Development Board. N.W.F.P. Small Scale Development Board, Pakistan: 1980. (Box PA-23)
      A Publication of Small Industries Advisory Service April 1980.
    - Woollen and Worsted Industry in West Pakistan. Jafari, S. J. Lahore, Directorate of Industries and Commerce, West Pakistan, Pakistan: 1968? (Box PA-23)
  - International Relations, 1950-1994, 3 boxes
    The 71 pamphlets in this section provide information on Pakistan's foreign policy; Pakistan's role in the non-aligned movement and the Commonwealth; state visits to other countries; and Pakistani reaction to India-Israel relations. Includes published statements from presidents - especially of Mohammad Zia-ul-Haq - and foreign ministers of Pakistan.
    - Address by General Mohammad Zia-ul-Haq, President, Islamic Republic of Pakistan, as Chairman of Islamic Conference at Thirty-fifth Session of United Nations General Assembly. Islamabad, Ministry of Information & Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1980. (Box PA-24)
      Wednesday, October 1, 1980.
    - Address by General Mohammad Zia-ul-Haq, President, Islamic Republic of Pakistan, at Seventh Non-Aligned Summit Conference, New Delhi, March 1983. Zia-ul-Haq, Mohammad. Islamabad, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, Pakistan: 1983. (Box PA-24)